reviewstore.org 2018-05-11

# ReviewStore.org | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At ReviewStore.org we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

It is ReviewStore.org’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, ReviewStore.org collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ReviewStore.org’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ReviewStore.org’s visitors use its website. From time to time, ReviewStore.org may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

ReviewStore.org also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments news/blog stories. ReviewStore.org only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

The amount and type of information that ReviewStore.org gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with ReviewStore.org – by purchasing a medication– are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each transactional case, ReviewStore.org uses a third party, such as ‘Health Solutions Network LLC’ who collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s purchase. ReviewStore.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

ReviewStore.org may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, ReviewStore.org may monitor the most popular pages on the site. ReviewStore.org may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ReviewStore.org does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

ReviewStore.org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ReviewStore.org’s behalf or to provide services available at ReviewStore.org’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ReviewStore.org’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ReviewStore.org will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ReviewStore.org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when ReviewStore.org believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ReviewStore.org, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of ReviewStore.org and have supplied your email address, ReviewStore.org may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with ReviewStore.org and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), this will be handled by a third party such as ‘Health Solutions Network LLC’. ReviewStore.org will not have access to this information sent via support email or any other feedback mechanism. ReviewStore.org takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ReviewStore.org uses cookies to help ReviewStore.org identify and track visitors, their usage of ReviewStore.org website, and their website access preferences. ReviewStore.org visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ReviewStore.org’s website, with the drawback that certain features of ReviewStore.org’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Business Transfers

If ReviewStore.org, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that ReviewStore.org goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of ReviewStore.org may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ReviewStore.org and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ReviewStore.org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ReviewStore.org’s sole discretion. ReviewStore.org encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
